[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to our
channel Money Mantra. Today I am
going to tell you about our company Tees India Marketing
Pvt. Ltd.,
what all work we do here. Let's start.
First of all, I will tell you a little bit about it.
We do a
very good job regarding health. We have a whole
team for it.
We work in about 12 to 13 companies.
But today I will tell you
about ICICI Lombard Health Insurance. We have a great company
in India which
gives the best quotation of ICICI Lombard and will tell you the best
premium. I will tell you its benefits.
Rest everything is the same in every policy.
Today I will
tell you the best benefit of it.
It is for newly married people.
Yes friends, this policy is very good for newly married people.
You must be curious to know why. What is there
in it? Let me tell you what is there in it for
newly married couples.
What does everyone do in this generation? If they
think of planning for a child early, then
someone  In any policy of any company, there is a
waiting period of 3 years or 2 years to cover pregnancy.
In our ICICI Lombard policy, yes,
in ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Company, there is a waiting period of only 9 months. So,
if you take a policy from today, then
you can cover that pregnancy in the next 9 months.
Yes friends, and there is
no limit to it. Even if it happens in any policy, there is
a limit in it, 40000,
25000, 20000, 10000, anything else
can be there, but in our company, there is no
limit in ECC loan, there is
no sub-limit. And its second
benefit is that whatever
child is born nowadays, it is a normal thing that he gets
vaccination, so whatever
vaccination the child gets, the sum insured for that child will
also remain the same, exactly the same.
Our company, ICICI Lombard, will
bear the expenses up to ₹1 lakh. Secondly,  B benefit is the
vaccination of the child, yes
friends, the vaccination for measles is also
called vaccination, whatever
vaccination will be done for it, that too will be given by our ICICI
Lombard, so
overall I would like to say that ICICI
Lombard is the best company for the health, so
my advice to you would be to get
your health insurance done as much as possible from this company and
for newly married people, this is the best and for
more information,
you can contact us anytime on the number given below, I will
provide you service any time, any time, okay
friends, let's go and subscribe to our channel,
like it, press the bell button,
share it as much as possible,
hello
[sangeet]
thank you h